Inventory of the Norman Allderdice Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Series I
  - Task Force for Do-It-Yourself Economic Self-Education, 1962. (Folder 43: 35)
  - Taxes, 1950s-1960s. (Folder 43: 36)
  - Taxpayers Committee to End Foreign Aid, 1969. (Folder 43: 37)
    List of budgetary requests for authorization and appropriations for foreign assistance for 1970
  - Tax fax, 1969. (Folder 43: 38)
  - Technocracy, Rushland, Pennsylvania, 1963-1964. (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Teen Age Republicans, Washington, D.C., 1965. (Folder 44: 2)
  - Television, 1969. (Folder 44: 3)
  - Tell 'm, 1962. (Folder 44: 4)
  - Tempe Peace Center, Tempe, Arizona, undated. (Folder 44: 5)
  - Texas Voters for Enforcing the Constitution, 1963. (Folder 44: 6)
    Clipping, printed matter, and related material
  - Texas Women for Constitutional Government, Houston, Texas, 1960s. (Folder 44: 7)
  - Third world politics, undated. (Folder 44: 8)
    Note
  - Thomas Dooley Foundation, San Francisco, California, 1964. (Folder 44: 9)
  - Thomas, Helen, Houston, Texas, 1954. (Folder 44: 10)
  - Thomas Jefferson Society of the United States of America, Hancock, New Hampshire, 1960s. (Folder 44: 11)
  - Threefold: A Movement Opposing Social Centralization, New York, 1960s. (Folder 44: 12)
  - Thunderbird Publication--Anti-Communist, Phoenix, Arizona, 1961. (Folder 44: 13)
  - Thurmond, Strom, 1963, 1972. (Folder 44: 14)
  - Thoreson, Inc., undated. (Folder 44: 15)
  - Through to victory, undated. (Folder 44: 16)
  - Today's World, St. Louis, Missouri, 1950s. (Folder 44: 17)
  - Tomorrow Press, 1967. (Folder 44: 18)
  - Torchbearers, Hawthorne, California, 1961. (Folder 44: 19)
  - Trade Policy Committee, Washington, D.C., 1960. (Folder 44: 20)
  - Train, San Marino, California, 1963. (Folder 44: 21)
  - Tri Continental Progressive Student Committee, undated. (Folder 44: 22)
  - Trinity College, 1958. (Folder 44: 23)
  - Triumph, undated. (Folder 44: 24)
  - Troy, Lillian Scott, 1930. (Folder 44: 25)
  - Truman administration, 1940s-1950s. (Folder 44: 26)
  - Truman, Harry S., undated. (Folder 44: 27)
  - Truth about Cuba Committee, Miami, Florida, 1961-1965; 1970s. (Folder 44: 28)
    Leaflets, newsletter, speech, statistical data, and related materials
  - Supreme Court Amendment League (SCALE), Washington, D.C., 1960s. (Folder 44: 29)
  - Truth about Civil Turmoil, Berkeley, California, 1968. (Folder 44: 30)
    Announcement, book reviews, leaflet, and related materials
  - Truth-Forum, 1962. (Folder 44: 31)
  - Truth Seeker, undated. (Folder 44: 32)
  - Tucson Board of Education, undated. (Folder 44: 33)
  - Tucson Chamber of Commerce, 1961. (Folder 44: 34)
    Minutes of meeting and report
  - Tucson Medical Center, 1955-1956. (Folder 44: 35)
    List of board of directors
  - Tucson Peace Center, Inc., 1968. (Folder 44: 36)
    Article and cover letter
  - Turn towards Peace, New York, 1960s. (Folder 44: 37)
    Form letter, leaflet, and related materials
  - Twentieth Century Evangelism, Pasadena, California, 1955-1960s. (Folder 44: 38)
    Address, article, leaflet, report, and printed matter
  - Twentieth Century Reformation Hour, Collingswood, New Jersey, 1959-1967. (Folder 44: 39-41)
    Form letter, leaflet, memorandum, newsletters, printed matter, and report
  - Twin Circle Publishing Company, undated. (Folder 44: 42)
  - Twin Cities Draft Information Center, 1969. (Folder 44: 43)
  - Twitty (Roy) Fund, Tucson, Arizona, 1966. (Folder 44: 44)
  - UMW Miners for Miller, Charleston, West Virginia, 1972. (Folder 44: 45)
  - Underground Press Syndicate, New York, 1960s. (Folder 44: 46)
  - Unemployment, Washington, D.C., 1940. (Folder 44: 47)
  - Unification Church, 1977. (Folder 44: 48)
  - Unions, 1960. (Folder 44: 49)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists--Anti-Nuclear, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1970. (Folder 44: 50)
  - United Church of Christ, 1957. (Box-folder 45: 1)
  - United Congressional Appeal, Washington, D.C., 1968. (Folder 45: 2)
  - United Committee to Save the Jewish State and the United Nations, New York, 1948. (Folder 45: 3)
  - United Farm Workers, San Francisco, California, 1974?. (Folder 45: 4)
  - United Features Syndicate, Inc., 1969. (Folder 45: 5)
  - United Group for Americanism in our Schools, 1956. (Folder 45: 6)
  - United Klans of America, Inc., 1966. (Folder 45: 7)
  - United Nations (Folder 45: 8-9)
    - General, 1947-1966.
      Clippings, form letters, newsletter, printed matter, report, and related materials
    - New York, 1951-1952. (Folder 45: 10)
      Background paper, bulletin, and leaflet
  - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF), 1958-1960. (Folder 45: 11)
    Clipping, fact sheet, and miscellany
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1951-1963. (Folder 45: 12)
    Article, printed matter, report, and related materials
  - United Nations Information Council of Missouri (UNICOM), 1965. (Folder 45: 13)
  - United College Negro Fund, 1972. (Folder 45: 14)
    Form letter, pamphlet, and miscellany
  - United Republicans of America, Washington, D.C., 1965-1968. (Folder 45: 15)
  - United Russian Anti-Communist Front, 1960s. (Folder 45: 16)
  - United Society of Methodist Laymen, undated. (Folder 45: 17)
  - U.S. aid to Europe, 1954-1957. (Folder 45: 18)
  - United States Anti-Communist Congress, Inc., Washington, D.C., 1968. (Folder 45: 19)
  - U.S. Census Bureau, 1968. (Folder 45: 20)
  - U.S. Committee for Democracy in Greece, Washington, D.C., 1967. (Folder 45: 21)
  - United States Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners, New York, 1966-1972. (Folder 45: 22)
  - United States Committee for the United Nations, 1959. (Folder 45: 23)
  - United States Conference of Mayors, 1958. (Folder 45: 24)
  - U.S. Congress, 1958. (Folder 45: 25)
    Article, clippings, and related materials
  - United States Constitution Sesquicentennial Commission, Washington, D.C., 1936-1939. (Folder 45: 26)
    Information sheets and program
  - United States Day Committee, Inc., Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1958. (Folder 45: 27)
    Announcement and miscellany
  - United States--"Executive Orders," Andrus, Margaret M., 1975. (Folder 45: 28)
  - United States Flag Committee, Jackson Heights, New York, 1955-1961. (Folder 45: 29)
    Fact sheet, flyer, letter, and related materials
  - United States Fuel Administration, 1915?. (Folder 45: 30)
  - United States Minuteman, undated. (Folder 45: 31)
  - United States Postal Service, 1954-1957. (Folder 45: 32)
  - U.S. Press Association, undated. (Folder 45: 33)
  - United States of America Publishing Company, 1964. (Folder 45: 34)
  - United States senators, 1958. (Folder 45: 35)
    Interviews
  - United States Steel Corporation, 1961. (Folder 45: 36)
  - United States War Veterans, Los Angeles, California, 1970?. (Folder 45: 37)
  - United World Federalists, Washington, D.C., 1968. (Folder 45: 38)
  - University of Arizona campus--Republicans, 1962. (Folder 45: 39)
    Leaflet and newsletter
  - University of Arizona Conservative Club, 1960s. (Folder 45: 40)
    Letter to President Kennedy
  - University of Arizona Young Republicans, Tucson, 1956-1962. (Folder 45: 41)
    Letter, minutes of meeting, and press release
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1946; 1957-1973. (Folder 45: 42)
    Clipping, flyers, and printed matter
  - University of Connecticut Medical Aid Committee, Storrs, Connecticut, undated. (Folder 45: 43)
  - University of Virginia Veterans for Peace, Richmond, Virginia, 1970. (Folder 45: 44)
    Letter to the governor
  - University Society of Individualists, Berkeley, California, 1960s. (Folder 45: 45)
    Information sheet and list of books
  - Urban League, 1956. (Folder 45: 46)
    Letter to the editor
  - Urban renewal, undated. (Folder 45: 47)
  - Vancouver Vietnam Day Committee, undated. (Folder 45: 48)
  - Vennard, Wickliffe B., 1950s. (Folder 45: 49)
  - Veritas Foundation, 1961-1967. (Folder 45: 50)
    Article, financial statement, and remarks
  - Veterans and Reservists to End the War in Vietnam, New York, 1966. (Folder 45: 51)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1959. (Folder 45: 52)
    Excerpts of remarks
  - Veterans of World War I, undated. (Folder 45: 53)
  - Victory without war campaign, Santa Ana, California, 1950s (Folder 45: 54)
  - Vietnam, 1967. (Box-folder 46: 1-2)
  - Victory in Vietnam Association, Oakland, California, 1965. (Folder 46: 3)
    Letter, list of sponsors, and miscellany
  - Vietnam, 1954-1973. (Folder 46: 4)
    Leaflet, report, speech, and related materials
  - "Vietnam: Challenge to Conscience,", 1966. (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Vietnam Courier, 1966. (Folder 47: 2)
  - Vietnam Democratic Party, 1962. (Folder 47: 3)
    Transcription of broadcast, press reports, and miscellany
  - Vietnam Solidarity Campaign, 1966. (Folder 47: 4)
    Article and policy statement
  - Vietnam Summer Project Committee, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1967. (Folder 47: 5)
  - Vietnam Youth Federation, 1973. (Folder 47: 6)
  - Vietnam Day Committee, 1965. (Folder 47: 7)
    Fact sheet, flyer, and newsletter
  - Viewpoint Books, 1967. (Folder 47: 8)
    Announcement, flyer, and miscellany
  - Vigilant Citizens of America, 1953. (Folder 47: 9)
  - Vigilant Women for the Bricker Amendment, Hinsdale, Illinois, 1955. (Folder 47: 10)
    Bulletin, form letter, and leaflet
  - Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government, 1964-1966. (Folder 47: 11)
    Brochures and printed matter
  - Voice of Americanism, 1970. (Folder 47: 12)
    Article and miscellany
  - Voice of Americanism broadcast, Glendale, California, 1966. (Folder 47: 13)
  - Volunteers for Goldwater, 1952. (Folder 47: 14)
  - Volunteers to Reelect Stafford and Cole, 1957. (Folder 47: 15)
  - Voters USA, Washington, D.C., 1961. (Folder 47: 16)
  - Wolfson, Louis E., 1972. (Folder 47: 17)
  - Walker Defense Fund, Dallas, Texas, undated. (Folder 47: 18)
  - Walker, Edwin A., Dallas, Texas, 1961-1964. (Folder 47: 19)
    Clipping, form letter, leaflet, and miscellany
  - Wallace, George C., Montgomery, Alabama, 1965-1972. (Folder 47: 20)
  - War Corporation, undated. (Folder 47: 21)
  - Warn, Keith L., undated. (Folder 47: 22)
    Request for information
  - War-Peace Report, New York, undated. (Folder 47: 23)
  - War Resisters' League, 1950-1966. (Folder 47: 24)
  - War Resisters' International, New York, 1964. (Folder 47: 25)
  - War tax resistance, New York, 1971. (Folder 47: 26)
  - Washington, D.C., sedition trial, 1944. (Folder 47: 27)
  - Washington summary, 1959. (Folder 47: 28)
  - Watch Washington Club, 1962. (Folder 47: 29)
  - Water, Agnes, 1953. (Folder 47: 30)
  - Watson, Albert W., undated. (Folder 47: 31)
  - Webster Quimmley Society, Garden Grove, California, 1963. (Folder 47: 32)
  - Welfare, 1970. (Folder 47: 33)
  - Western Conference of Teamsters, San Francisco, California, 1973. (Folder 47: 34)
    Leaflet, memorandum, and miscellany
  - Western Hemisphere Evangelical Union, Inc., 1961. (Folder 47: 35)
  - We the People
    - General, 1966, 1968. (Folder 47: 36)
    - Chicago, Illinois, 1955-1965. (Folder 47: 37)
      Flyer, form letter, leaflet, and miscellany
    - San Francisco, California, 1961-1962. (Folder 47: 38)
  - Whetmore, James E., California, 1970. (Folder 47: 39)
    Letter and leaflet
  - White American, undated. (Folder 47: 40)
    Thank you note
  - Whitneys, Chicago, Illinois, 1959. (Folder 47: 41)
  - Wiggins, Charles E., Fullerton, California, 1976. (Folder 47: 42)
  - Wilderness Society, 1967. (Folder 47: 43)
  - Willard, Mercier C., undated. (Folder 47: 44)
  - Willkie, Wendell, 1940. (Folder 47: 45)
  - Winchell, Walter, undated. (Folder 47: 46)
  - Women for Peace, undated. (Folder 47: 47)
  - Women Investors Research Institute, Washington, D.C., 1957-1959. (Folder 47: 48)
    Remarks, report, and speech
  - Women Office Workers Conference, 1973. (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - Women's Division, Democratic National Committee, Washington, D.C., 1961. (Folder 48: 2)
    Workshop program
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1962-1968. (Folder 48: 3)
    Article, statement, and miscellany
  - Women's Legislative Committee, 1962. (Folder 48: 4)
    Minutes of meeting
  - Women's liberation, 1971. (Folder 48: 5)
    Article, printed matter, remarks, and related materials
  - Women's National Crusade, 1950?. (Folder 48: 6)
  - Women's voice, Chicago, Illinois, 1954-1955. (Folder 48: 7)
    Article, clippings, leaflets, and printed matter
  - Worker's Music League, New York, 1933. (Folder 48: 8)
  - Worker's Defense League, New York, 1963. (Folder 48: 9)
  - Working Americans Bicentennial Project, Washington, D.C., 1970s. (Folder 48: 10)
  - Workshop against Subversion, 1955. (Folder 48: 11)
  - World Academy, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1970. (Folder 48: 12)
  - World Assembly for Moral Rearmament, 1955. (Folder 48: 13)
  - World Committee for a World Constitutional Convention, Denver, Colorado, 1963. (Folder 48: 14)
  - World Constitution Coordinating Committee, Phoenix, Arizona, 1962-1963. (Folder 48: 15)
    Letter to the editor, press release, and summary report
  - World Council of Churches, undated. (Folder 48: 16)
  - World Health Organization (WHO), 1958. (Folder 48: 17)
    Article and statement
  - World Labor Zionist Movement, 1969-1970. (Folder 48: 18)
  - World Peace Broadcasting Foundation, Des Moines, Iowa, 1960-1966. (Folder 48: 19-20)
    Address, announcement, leaflet, printed matter, report, and related materials
  - World Political Parties and Groups Institute, New York, 1973. (Folder 48: 21)
  - World Prophetic Ministry, Colton, California, 1973. (Folder 48: 22)
  - World University Roundtable, 1964. (Folder 48: 23)
  - World Union of National Socialists, Arlington, Virginia, 1960. (Folder 48: 24)
  - World War II--Pacific theater, 1940-1941. (Folder 48: 25)
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, Inc., 1966.
    Letter, memorandum, and miscellany
    - New York, 1965. (Folder 48: 26)
    - Bloomington, Indiana, 1966. (Folder 48: 27)
      Letters and memorandum
  - Wright, Orville and Wilbur, 1933. (Folder 48: 28)
    Broadcast transcript
  - Yalta Agreement, 1945. (Folder 48: 29)
  - YAUNEH, Columbia University, New York, 1960s. (Folder 48: 30)
  - Yippies, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1960s. (Folder 48: 31)
  - Yoga for health, 1962. (Folder 48: 32)
  - Voice of America, 1953-1956. (Folder 48: 33)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1961-1967. (Folder 48: 34)
    Article, bulletin, flyer, and printed matter
  - Young Democrats, 1960s. (Folder 48: 35)
  - Young, Glen, O., 1960. (Folder 48: 36)
  - Young Republicans, 1973-1975. (Folder 48: 37)
  - Young Socialists for Halstead and Boutelle, 1968. (Folder 48: 38)
  - Young Voters for the President, Virginia, 1972. (Folder 48: 39)
  - Young Peoples Socialist League, New York, 1960s. (Folder 48: 40)
  - Youth Federation for Freedom, Washington, D.C., 1964. (Folder 48: 41)
  - Youth for the Voluntary Prayer Amendment, Houston, Texas, 1966. (Folder 48: 42)
  - Youth Publishers, New York, 1935. (Folder 48: 43)
  - Yugoslavia, undated. (Folder 48: 44)
  - Zero Population Growth, Los Altos, California, 1970. (Folder 48: 45)
- Series II (Box 49)
  - A. A. Allen Revivals, Inc.
    - "Witchcraft, Wizards and Witches,", 1968. (Folder 49: 1)
    - "Does God Heal through Medicine?" (Folder 49: 2)
    - "Is Your Sickness a Thorn in the Flesh?", undated. (Folder 49: 3)
    - "My Vision of the Destruction of America Atop Empire State Building,", 1954. (Folder 49: 4)
    - "7 Other Spirits: A Revelation of the Underground Forces of a Sinister Enemy,", 1953. (Folder 49: 5)
  - A. A. Johnson and Associates--"Pocket Paragraphs on the Soviet Union,", 1932. (Folder 49: 6)
  - A. F. of L. labor unions--Trumbo, Dalton, "An Open Letter to ...", 1942. (Folder 49: 7)
  - AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C., "Collective bargaining,", 1959. (Folder 49: 8)
    Conference proceedings
  - AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C., "Labor Looks at Congress, 1969,", 1970. (Folder 49: 9)
    Legislative report
  - AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C., "Labor Looks at the 88th Congress,", 1964. (Folder 49: 10)
  - AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C., Committee on Political Education--"How your Senators and Representatives ...,", 1947-1962, undated. (Folder 49: 11-14)
    Reports
  - AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C.--Maritime Trades Department--"MTD's 20 Point Program,", undated. (Folder 49: 15)
  - A. I. P.--"Cuba: Terror and Death, Once Again ...,", undated. (Folder 49: 16)
  - A. J. Macdonald and Associates--"Kangaroo Court ...,", 1963. (Folder 49: 17)
  - Acacia Mutual Life Insurance Company--Kacy, Howard W., "Wake up America,", undated. (Folder 49: 18)
  - Acorn Press--"Communist Penetration and Subversion of the Belgian Congo," Bartlett, Robert E., Jr., 1962. (Folder 49: 19)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Triple Revolution, 1964. (Folder 49: 20)
  - "Administration of Occupied Countries in Eastern Europe,", 1941. (Folder 49: 21)
  - Advancement Committee--Burke, Arthur, 1946. (Folder 49: 22)
  - Advertising Council--"Challenge to Americans,", 1963. (Folder 49: 23)
  - Alabama Legislative Commission to Preserve the Peace--"Biennial Report to the Alabama ...,", 1965 (Folder 49: 24)
  - Alert--Gibbons, Edward H., "It's your Move ...,", 1951. (Folder 49: 25)
  - Alliance, Inc.--"Brainwashing and Senator McCarthy," Kornfeder, Joseph Z., 1954. (Folder 49: 26)
  - Alliance, Inc.--"Heredity, and Civilization ...," George, W., Race, 1963. (Folder 49: 27)
  - "Alternative Perspectives on Vietnam,", 1965. (Folder 49: 28)
  - Amazing Prophecy Center--"The Coming World Dictator ...," Clark, Doug, undated. (Folder 49: 29)
  - Ambassador College
    - "The New Feminism ...,", 1970. (Folder 49: 30)
    - "The Wonderful World ...," Armstrong, Herbert W., and Ted Garner, 1966. (Folder 49: 31)
  - American Afro-Asian Education Exchange--Chieh, "Should Peiping Be ...,", 1966. (Folder 49: 32)
  - American Afro-Asian Education Exchange--Tsiang, Tingfu F., "Freedom vs. Communism ...,", undated. (Folder 49: 33)
  - American Arbitration Association--"Voluntary Labor ...,", undated. (Folder 49: 34)
  - American Assembly--"Prisoners in America ...,", 1972. (Folder 49: 35)
  - American Bar Association
    - "Peaceful Co-existence...,", 1961. (Folder 49: 36)
    - "Resolutions and Report...,", 1960. (Folder 49: 37)
    - Sullivan, William C., 1965. (Box-folder 50: 1)
      Lectures
  - American-Christian Palestine Committee, Voss, Carl H., 1948. (Folder 50: 2)
  - American Citizen--"The Rebels...," Wade, Martin J., 1927. (Folder 50: 3)
  - American Civil Liberties Union
    - "The Case against Death Penalty," Bedau, Hugo A., 1973. (Folder 50: 4)
    - "By the People ...,", 1959-1960. (Folder 50: 5)
    - "Freedom through ...,", 1961-1962. (Folder 50: 6)
    - "New Dimensions ...,", 1965-1967. (Folder 50: 7)
    - Southern California branch--"The Liberals and the War Crisis," McWilliams, Carey, 1940. (Folder 50: 8)
    - Northern California--"Prelude to a Red Hunt,", 1947. (Folder 50: 9)
    - "Security and Freedom,", 1951. (Folder 50: 10)
      Annual report and printed matter
    - "Prosecution of Mary Ware Dennett for Obscenity,", 1929. (Folder 50: 11)
    - "What Is the American Civil ...,", 1960. (Folder 50: 12)
    - "Watergate and Civil ...,", 1973. (Folder 50: 13)
  - American Coalition of Patriotic Societies
    - "Meditations of Joseph Stalin," Watson, Emile E., 1952. (Folder 50: 14)
    - "U.N. Judgment Day," Widener, Alice, 1953. (Folder 50: 15)
      Study
    - "Resolutions,", 1961. (Folder 50: 16)
    - "Soviet Espionage...," Willoughby, Charles A., 1957. (Folder 50: 17)
  - American Commentator Publishing Company--"ABC on Communism," Fawkes, E. W., 1949. (Folder 50: 18)
  - American Committee for Cultural Freedom--"Heresy, Yes ...," Hook, Sidney, undated. (Folder 50: 19)
  - American Committee for Justice in the Middle East--Nes, David G.
    - "The June War,", 1968. (Folder 50: 20)
    - "Peace in the Middle East...,", 1970. (Folder 50: 21)
  - American Committee for Protection of Foreign-Born
    - "The Schneiderman Case: ...," with introduction by Carol King, 1943. (Folder 50: 22-23)
    - "Our Badge of Infamy,", 1959. (Folder 50: 24)
    - "The Registration of Aliens," Marcantonio, Vito, 1940. (Folder 50: 25)
  - American Committee on Immigration Policies--"Our Immigration System,", 1964-1965. (Folder 50: 26-27)
  - American Conservative Union--"Nixon Welfare Plan,", 1970. (Folder 50: 28)
  - American Council for Judaism
    - "A Question of Time,", 1956. (Folder 50: 29)
      Scrapbook
    - "Zionism: Tribalism or Liberalism?" Cohen, Morris R., 1946. (Folder 50: 30)
    - "UJA Funds ...," Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1960?. (Folder 50: 31)
      Report?
  - American Council of Christian Laymen
    - "Let's Revive the ...,", undated. (Folder 50: 32)
      Postcard
    - "The Federal Council of Churches--Takes Its Stand," Kaub, Verne P., 1950?. (Folder 50: 33)
    - "Let us Protestants Awake," Markham, Reuben H., 1949. (Folder 50: 34)
  - American Council of Race Relations--"Hemmed In ...,", 1945. (Folder 50: 35)
  - American Eagle Publishing Company
    - "Law of the ...," Surrey, R. A., undated. (Folder 50: 36)
      Address?
    - Walker, Edwin A.
      - "Walker Speaks ... Unmuzzled,", 1962. (Folder 50: 37)
        Speeches
      - "Walker Speaks ... on Textbooks,", 1962. (Folder 50: 38)
        Testimony
      - "What Is Counterinsurgency?", undated. (Folder 50: 39)
  - American Economic Foundation
    - "How We Live in ...," Baker, Katherine J., and Lillie B. Shearin, 1960. (Folder 50: 40)
      Manual
    - "The Indispensable ...," Clark, Fred G., 1963. (Folder 50: 41)
    - "Economics in Teacher ...," West, Roscoe L., 1958. (Folder 50: 42)
    - "Problem Is People,", 1965. (Folder 50: 43)
    - "Nature's Despotism," Rustgard, John, undated. (Folder 50: 44)
    - "To Tell the Truth to All ...,", 1964-1965. (Folder 50: 45)
      Souvenir book
  - American Education Association
    - McDonald, Milo F.
      - "American Education ...,", 1952. (Folder 50: 46)
      - "Progressive Poison ...,", 1951. (Folder 50: 47)
    - Vinson, Mary, "Test for Literacy,", 1954. (Box-folder 51: 1)
  - American Enterprise Association
    - "Involuntary Participation ...," Bradley, Philip D., 1956. (Folder 51: 2)
    - "International Labor Organization ...," Calhoun, Leonard J., 1953. (Folder 51: 3)
    - "Private Investments Abroad," Carroll, Charles R., 1954. (Folder 51: 4)
    - "Three Taft-Hartley Issues," Iserman, Theodore R., 1955. (Folder 51: 5)
    - "Legal Immunities ...," Pound, Roscoe, 1957. (Folder 51: 6)
    - "State Rights and the Law of Labor ...," Reilly, George D., 1955. (Folder 51: 7)
  - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research
    - "War Powers Bill,", 1972. (Folder 51: 8)
    - "Legal Services Corporation Bill,", 1973. (Folder 51: 9)
    - "1973 Sessions of the Congress--Review,", 1974. (Folder 51: 10)
    - "Sections 235 and 236 ...," Wehner, Harrison G., Jr., 1972. (Folder 51: 11)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations
    - "Constitution of ...,", 1967?. (Folder 51: 12)
    - "Facts vs. ...,", 1957. (Folder 51: 13)
    - "Labor Looks at Automation,", 1959. (Folder 51: 14)
    - "Labor Looks at the 91st Congress,", 1971. (Folder 51: 15)
    - "Survey of ...,", 1975. (Folder 51: 16)
    - "Why Unions?", 1957. (Folder 51: 17)
  - American Federation of Labor News Service--"President Green Sounds ...,", undated. (Folder 51: 18)
  - American Friends of Captive Nations--"Hungary under Soviet ...,", undated. (Folder 51: 19)
  - American Friends Service Committee
    - Davidson, Bill, 1952. (Folder 51: 20)
    - Fromm, Erich, "War within Man,", 1963. (Folder 51: 21)
      Series of studies
    - Fleming, D. F., "Does Deterrence Deter?", 1962. (Folder 51: 22)
    - Horowitz, Irving Louis, "Games, Strategies and Peace,", 1963. (Folder 51: 23)
      Studies